There's so many beautiful stained glass pieces to choose from.
It almost seems silly to incorporate other things, but why not?
Sometimes I like to use little glitter glass in my pieces or glass beads.
You can also feel free to use little tiles, some come in shapes already precut for you.
These are glass flowers.
They're Italian made, they're called millifiore, million flowers.
They can add nice little highlights and touches in your pieces.
You can even add soveniers.
This is a Buddha from a trip I took to Thailand.
It will look beautiful in a piece.
Here's an example of a piece in which I used a couple of multimedia highlights.
Most of this is stained glass, but I have a glass bead up here, I have glitter glass windows, the Millifiore flowers as a doorknob, and flowers in the grass.
It adds texture, depth, and a touch of class.
Here's another example.
In this piece, I used stained glass to make the bamboo, I used tempered glass for the background.
Tempered glass is really easy to find in a city like SanFransisco when people get their car windows broken.
It's also easy to find if you know contractors who break down shower doors or shower windows.
All that glass is tempered and can make a beautiful sparkling effect on your piece.
Remember, you have a lot of creativity in this project so be creative, go wild, go crazy, use colors or don't.
Just enjoy the process, be patient with yourself and have a good time.